Hello
Hello everyone
I'm Qimiao, uh
In this episode, let's introduce GVA
the updates in version 2.8.9
Updates in version 2.8.9
Let's take a brief look first
The first improvement is the optimization of the AI experience
Adjusted AI usage methods
This adjustment was actually made in the backend.
I reduced the mutual calls between AI microservices.
accelerated the overall AI process
Uh
in your usage
Actually, there's no need for any significant adjustments
Mainly, I've made some changes in the backend.
Then there's the AI Pass, um
Previously, the AI pass in the plugin marketplace required an application.
Now in version 2.8.9, there is a new AI pass called AIRPODS
It will be automatically provided to you when you enter the page
No need to apply anymore
Um
In subsequent version 2.8.9, you'll need to use the new AI Pass.
You can just make the changes yourself.
This is the fast one
The fast old one can still be used.
Versions before 2.8.9 can also be used
but it's the slower AI, okay
These are things that everyone gradually experiences
It won't have a real impact
The third is the 2.5 version of the plugin
Plugins now support automatic installation
deleted
You can also see all the things installed by the plugin.
Then the V2 version of the plugin
just need a single sentence to confirm
Upgrade to version 2.5
Plugin authors need to, uh, upgrade this
and uh then then that that that uh
We'll show you one in a moment
a demonstration of the V2.5 plugin
Now there's no need to add any code either
Just need to put the zip file in
Simply install it and it's ready to use
No need to add another line yourself
things like comments or anything like that
Another feature that has been added is
login log feature
Another one is the API call token issuance.
this token template thing
This makes it convenient for everyone to use it to develop backend APIs
and then expose it for others to use
Then, the template has added a tag validation
Often, some friends would on the page, uh,
on the page
then click on that tag
clicking and suddenly turning white
No idea what's going on.
Actually, it's because there are multiple DOMs under this template
resulting in the failure of the VOE UGC Anime function
So we've added a check
when it fails
a pop-up alert will appear to inform you
Make this change and it'll be good
Another one is skills management.
Our GVA must always keep up with the development of AI
to enhance our capabilities
We are always committed to developing for AI.
To create the framework that understands AI best and is best understood by AI, haha, good.
So this is a brief overview
Now let's officially take a look at a few features.
Let's skip these two
we won't demonstrate that
Now let's take a look at this 2.5 version
Now, our plugin system's plugin
At the bottom of the installation page, you can see which plugins we've installed.
For example, this one, right?
Uh, that is... Which plugin is this again?
This is that demo plugin of ours.
that is, with the email plugin
that that that that that that
This small functional plugin, right?
Which one is site-wide
Which one is the backend?
Let's first demonstrate the uninstallation of the plugin
Let's take a look at the backend
There is a plugin here
Now we are on the plugin installation page
The frontend also has it
The front end also needs to check, there's also this, uh,
in the plugin ping
There's also this plugin, right?
Then we now click delete
get rid of it
after that
It's gone now.
The frontend will also be removed
This backend plugin will also be removed
It will be done automatically
and there's an injection in here that will be gone
will be gone
Next, we will demonstrate the plugin installation.
During installation
Let's restart now
Let's restart first
After the restart
You can see the announcement management of our previous plugin system
This is already gone
See
The external one is no longer there
Because the menu was not entered
So you can still see one here
Now we just need to install it
Just drag it over
Just drag it over from here
Ah, in this way it's installed.
After installation, you can see the backend is the backend
It will be automatically installed for you here.
Then the plugin will be automatically registered here
We no longer need to do this manually.
Now you just need to update it
update the backend
You'll notice that our previous
The installed content is back again.
This is our 2.5 version plugin
Finally, there's no need to add that line of code anymore.
Ah, I was just being lazy back then.
It's also because I was lazy.
You see, now we have the API paths listed, right?
Then we have how many menus, right
How many of these functional things are there?
will all be listed uh
This is the original page.
Here this is the Home page
This plugin is a built-in demo plugin for the system
So it has some slight differences compared to regular plugins.
so just ignore it
Your experience during actual usage will be just as good as what you saw earlier
Next, let's take a look at the login log feature
The demonstration of this feature is actually quite straightforward.
The login log is actually a capability that was previously lacking.
It's just been added now.
There is a login log in our system tools
Here's every single login record, right?
All this device information and stuff will be recorded.
Then there's our API token issuance
Previously,
this API token
this position
Some friends mentioned that they want to share an API with others
expose a segment of our API
However, they don't want to show them the backend for login
So this is where you can issue it
Select a user when issuing
Just select the corresponding role and issue it for them.
After signing, there will be a token.
Take note of it yourselves
Actually, it's not a big deal if you don't jot this down here
because we also have a CRUD demonstration
in the demo of cod
you can put this token in the header
or put this token in the cookie
both are acceptable
Both methods are stored for you
You can take them and use them directly for the clients
The client will know how to use it
Okay, this is the API demonstration feature.
Another feature is the single DOM detection under the template
Let me demonstrate this for you.
Let's say
Let's take the plugin we just installed as an example.
Suppose you can see there is a DOM here, right?
there is a div
Now let's add another div
Add another div1122 under the template
Now save and return to the page
you will find that
we refresh and uh
Enter the previously developed page
Hey, look, it will tell you
it says there are multiple root nodes here
and then tell you how to fix it
Hey why is that
Because in the case of multiple root nodes
We are not fixing it now
Look, I jump and the screen goes blank, right?
This is the most, most, most important reason for it.
So now when we enter the page
will perform a check
After the detection is completed
just give it a
After you come back, follow this prompt
delete it
After deleting it, this prompt won't appear anymore, right?
This prompt will no longer appear
Then the previous white screen issue won't occur either
This is to prevent everyone from making such incorrect coding behaviors.
Okay, another final and quite significant one.
Well, actually this is not very
It's not that I've provided you with some capabilities
This is a capability I've opened up called skills management
Now skills have become an essential part of AI development
a necessary step
So we can do a good job here
some global constraints of scales
For example, in this constraint here
The Go diagram will ultimately interact with JS's Qisen
Just write this to supplement the unified constraints and specifications of the tool, right?
We can just save it directly
After saving
After synchronization is complete
You'll find that I'll help you
I will help you under the main body of GVA
I'll open a new window
Open another uh
Look at this
This is to create SCALLS for you under the ontology
and its global constraints
And then, some friends
Actually, you would spend some time learning these scales
may still take you a little more time
I just helped you save that little bit of time
You can create a skill here
I'll tell you what's inside this skill creation
What are these functions for?
For example, let's call it code code
The name is Test
At this point, I will automatically create a scales template for you.
See
What do you want to do here
Right, uh
The content written here
Then, uh, what each field does
I've told you everything
You write according to this standard
skills can be used directly
And there will also be title instructions here
how you should use it
I can add them all in for you, yes
Some main content has been pre-scheduled for you in advance.
Then if you need to write a script
Scripts can also be created here
These scripts will also
It means you only need to operate from the page.
What he created must be a usable
it must be a usable thing
it must be something that the AI recognizes
Save this
In this way, these contents will be available
Then after saving it
We save the configuration
Then synchronize
All these SCALLS will be created for you
For example, there are these things in the code, right
This is what we just wrote
a script for each of the scales
The format has also been fully organized for you.
Then, the scripts you wrote will be placed under the script.
You just need to write it here, alright
it will tell you
I will call it now
what to do at this time
This is a SCALLS approach
writing method
ensure that you can achieve with minimal learning effort
to create a scale that better suits your own needs
In future versions
JVA will also create many
this scale that helps everyone write code
or incorporate scales that help improve work efficiency
This will further deepen the integration between our framework and AI.
Of course, if you want to provide me with some Scouts
You are also very welcome to submit PRs on GitHub.
I think it's good
I will include all of them for you
You can also submit to the plugin marketplace if you want to make money.
No, no, it's all not possible, not possible.
Alright then, that's all for this episode
That's all for now
That's all.
We will further integrate the framework with AI in the future
We aim to make it more AI-savvy and AI-aware
a more intelligent framework
make this JVA the best technical framework for development in the AI era
the best technical framework
That's all for this episode.
See you in the next episode